Guide to the Harold and Joyce Pomeroy Schwartz Public Art Archive 1961-2009 (bulk 1976-2005) MSS.171
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Administrative Files
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Hirshhorn S.G., undated (Box 50, Folder 35)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: MOMA, undated (Box 50, Folder 36)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Munster, undated (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: NOAA, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Noguchi, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Other, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Sculpture Parks and Gardens: Socrates, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Storm King, undated (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Villa Celle, undated (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Sculpture Parks & Gardens: Walker A. Center, undated (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Sculpture: Post 1965, undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Sculpture: Shinjuku, undated (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Sculpture: Villa Celle, undated (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Seating, undated (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Seattle, undated (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Schiffler Collection, undated (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Shopping Centers, undated (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - SITE, undated (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Slides - Untitled, undated (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Slides - Untitled, undated (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Slides - Untitled, undated (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Soho Art Walking Tours, undated (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Sound Sculpture, undated (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Space Exhibition, undated (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Storm King Art Center, undated (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Street Life, undated (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Studio in a School, undated (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Sunday Salons - Art & Politics from the Heart, undated (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Suzanne Randolphe, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 27)
  - Tampa, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 28)
  - Thematical Art - Abstract Art, 1980-1986 (Box 51, Folder 29)
  - Thematical Art - Ancient Traditional & Historical, undated (Box 51, Folder 30)
  - Thematical Art - Folk Art - Ethnic Art, undated (Box 51, Folder 31)
  - Thematical Art - Figurative Sculpture, undated (Box 51, Folder 32)
  - Thematical Art - Honour in Art, undated (Box 51, Folder 33)
  - Thematical Art - Monumental Sculpture, undated (Box 51, Folder 34)
  - Tillet Lighting Design, Inc., undated (Box 51, Folder 35)
  - Tochigi - Lita Albuquerque, 1996 (Box 51, Folder 36)
  - Tokyo Intern Art Forum, 1995-1996 (Box 51, Folder 37)
  - Tokyo/NY Sister Cities, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 38)
  - Tomi - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 39)
  - Tomi - Kiosks, 1997-1998 (Box 51, Folder 40)
  - Tomi - Proposal, undated (Box 51, Folder 41)
  - Toppenishi Mural Project, 1993-1994 (Box 51, Folder 42)
  - Transformations, undated (Box 51, Folder 43)
  - Transportation, 1983-1995 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Transportation, 1991-1996; 2001 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Transportation, 1994-1995 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Transpotomac Canal - Poiriers, undated (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Unfoldered materials [1 of 4], undated (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Unfoldered materials [2 of 4], undated (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Unfoldered materials [3 of 4], undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Unfoldered materials [4 of 4], undated (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Urban Design, 1989; 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Urban Design, 1994-1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Urban Design - 'Saginaw Buys a Solstice Machine', undated (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Urbanism, 1990; 1999-2002 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Urbanism, 2001-2002 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Urbanism, 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Urbanism Stadiums, 2005 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Van Allen, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Venet Project, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Venice, 1995 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Video Art, 2006 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Video Info, undated (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Vietnam Memorial: Controversy, 1982-1988 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Dwan, 2003 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Von Schlegell Proposals [1 of 2], undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Von Schlegell Proposals [2 of 2], undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Wanas Foundation, undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Water Fountains, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Websites (of interest), undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Women's Owned Business, undated (Box 52, Folder 28)
  - World Trade, 2001 (Box 52, Folder 29)
  - World Trade Center Memorials, 2001-2004 (Box 52, Folder 30)
  - World Wide Web article, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 31)
  - WPA, 2002 (Box 52, Folder 32)
  - WWII, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 33)
  - WWII Memorial GSA, 1996 (Box 52, Folder 34)
- Series III: Data Storage
  The Scope and Content Notes at individual item levels reflect any original writing on the compact disk or cover.
  Compact disks in this series were removed from their original folders from Series I and II.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Data storage disks have not been preserved and are currently unavailable to researchers.
  - Albuquerque, Lita, ID: 171.3.0001 (Box 55, Folder 1, Media ID: 171.3.0001)
    Public Art
  - Aycock, Alice, 2000-2004; ID: 171.3.0002 (Box 55, Folder 2, Media ID: 171.3.0002)
    New Work
  - Aycock, Alice, December 21, 2004; ID: 171.3.0003 (Box 55, Folder 2, Media ID: 171.3.0003)
    Proposals in Florida & Cincinnati
  - Aycock, Alice, ID: 171.3.0004 (Box 55, Folder 2, Media ID: 171.3.0004)
    Various Works
  - Bishop Good, Francie, ID: 171.3.0005 (Box 55, Folder 3, Media ID: 171.3.0005)
    Scope and Contents
    Francie Bishop Good 3 Animations
  - Bishop Good, Francie, ID: 171.3.0006 (Box 55, Folder 3, Media ID: 171.3.0006)
    11 Files Fyi from Francie Bishop Good
  - Bishop Good, Francie, ID: 171.3.0007 (Box 55, Folder 3, Media ID: 171.3.0007)
    FBGood Florida Show
  - Brown, Carol, ID: 171.3.0008 (Box 55, Folder 4, Media ID: 171.3.0008)
    Carol K. Brown, 305-532-3081 Digital Frame .avi files Carol K. Brown, 164 E. 14th St. 25"x11.5"x2.5 1701 Lake Ave. Apt. 308 18"x24.5"x2.5" 21 Nassau Dr. 14"x30"x3" all - 2002, wood & LCD screens
  - Christo & Jeanne-Claude, ID: 171.3.0009 (Box 55, Folder 5, Media ID: 171.3.0009)
    The Gates ALL PIX RAW 327 pix
  - Davidow, Julie, ID: 171.3.0010 (Box 55, Folder 6, Media ID: 171.3.0010)
    Julie Davidow Disc Four: Images w/ ("petri #1-#12")
  - Edelstein, Barbara, ID: 171.3.0011 (Box 55, Folder 7, Media ID: 171.3.0011)
    same compact disk and cover as found in Folder 24.
    compact disk: Elemental Spring: Guangzhou, Elemental Spring: Hangzhou, Ink Rock Water, Elemental Spring: Shenzhen Project, Wind/Weed Wind/Water, Nectar for Neptune Barbara Edelstein
    CD cover booklet: Barbara Edelstein, a native of Los Angeles, was exposed to the cultures of both shores of the Pacific in her early years. The geographical proximity and cultural blending of the Asian and the American traditions had a significant impact on her way of thinking, and later cultivated in her a unique style of Zen artistry. Barbara's artworks continually reflect water as both a concrete material and an abstract concept - a dualism that bridges the natural and the artistic worlds. The flow of water in her artworks communicates a motion that transcends time, an elevation of spirituality, and a delicate form of expression that is the epitome of feminism. "The environment plays a large part in how I formulate my work. I have strived to unite nature and the metropolitan culture in a graceful balance... I put into my artworks both the products of nature and processed materials. The purpose is to recreate a new kind of harmony in which the spirit of nature is eternal." Thus, one may speculate that Barbara's artworks are the extensions of nature, or that nature has become an integral component of her artistic expression.
    Elemental Spring: Guangzhou, 2002, 18'x16'x14', copper, water, Guangdong Museum of Art, Guangzhou, China Elemental Spring: Hangzhou, 2001, 10'x6'x5', copper, water, West Lake, Hangzhou, China Ink Rock Water, #1, 2, 3, 2002, #1: 96"x28"x24", #2: 28"x34"x24", #3: 32"x28"x25", ink rock, petrified wood, copper, sumi-ink, water, Guangdong Museum of Art, Guangzhou, China Elemental Spring: Shenzhen Project, 2002, size variable, copper, water, video, sound, Shenzhen Art Institute, Shenzhen, China Wind/Weed Wind/Water, 1994, 5'x12'x14', water, weeds, wind, Djerassi Sculpture Park, Woodside, California, U.S.A. Nectar for Neptune, 1990, 40'x61'x91', horsechestnut tree, Neptune Pool, water, Snug Harbor Cultural Center, Staten Island, New York, U.S.A.
  - Fry, Leslie, 2006; ID: 171.3.0012 (Box 55, Folder 8, Media ID: 171.3.0012)
    cover: Leslie Fry Commissions, www.LeslieFry.com compact disk: Leslie Fry Public Art
  - Gelfman, Lynne Golob, ID: 171.3.0013 (Box 55, Folder 9, Media ID: 171.3.0013)
    Joyce Schwartz Selects (by Dan) Lynne Golob Gelfman Images 040221 Low Res
  - Gelfman, Lynne Golob, ID: 171.3.0014 (Box 55, Folder 9, Media ID: 171.3.0014)
    Lynne Gelfman (by Tim) [ostrgard] 4 images & 2 Joyce S. viewing.
  - Glier, Mike, 1987-2001; ID: 171.3.0015 (Box 55, Folder 10, Media ID: 171.3.0015)
    www.williams.edu/Art/glier Mike Glier
  - Glier, Mike, 2004; ID: 171.3.0016 (Box 55, Folder 10, Media ID: 171.3.0016)
    Mike Glier's Town Green in the making, Cambridge City TV, 2004, 30:00
  - Held, Al, 2005; ID: 171.3.0017 (Box 55, Folder 11, Media ID: 171.3.0017)
    3-05 JPS PIX of 53rd St Station - Al Held
  - Held, Al, 2005; ID: 171.3.0018 (Box 55, Folder 11, Media ID: 171.3.0018)
    Al Held Mem. Oct.
  - Held, Al, 2005; ID: 171.3.0019 (Box 55, Folder 11, Media ID: 171.3.0019)
    Al Held Memorial Sept. 2005
  - LeWitt, Sol, ID: 171.3.0020 (Box 55, Folder 12, Media ID: 171.3.0020)
    3-05 JPS PIX of Sol LeWitt in Pittsburgh
  - Lobe, Robert, ID: 171.3.0021 (Box 55, Folder 13, Media ID: 171.3.0021)
    Bob Lobe, 1976-2005, Powerpoint
  - Nagasawa, Nobuho, 2002; ID: 171.3.0022 (Box 55, Folder 14, Media ID: 171.3.0022)
    Nobuho Nagasawa Portfolio 2002, nobuho2001@yahoo.com
  - Norzick, Lori, 2005; ID: 171.3.0023 (Box 55, Folder 15, Media ID: 171.3.0023)
    cover: Lori Nozick, email: Lnozickart@aol.com, P.O. Box 771 98 Paulding Lane, Crompond, NY 10517 USA, 914.603.3187, 9144731588 Cell compact disk: Lori Nozick c. 2005 Portfolio
  - Oursler, Tony, ID: 171.3.0024 (Box 55, Folder 16, Media ID: 171.3.0024)
    NYEHAUS Tony Oursler: Sound Digressions in Seven Colors, Opening: Saturday, February 25th, 7-9P, February 25th to March 25th 2006, 15 Gramercy Park South, #8D New York, NY 10003, Hours of Operation: Tuesday-Saturday (11AM-6PM), T: 212.995.1785, F: 212.473.4994, INFO@NYEHAUS.COM, WWW.NYEHAUS.COM, Featuring: Tony Conrad: Antique School Bells, Kim Gordon: Bass, Etc. Ikue Mori:Computer, Zeena Parkins: Electric Harp, Lee Ranaldo: Guitar & Small Devices, J.G. Thirlwell: Aquasonic, Stephen Vitiello: Photocell & Electronics, Produced by Tony Oursler and Tim NYE. Mix by Tony Oursler and Dan Walsh.
  - Schmacke, Claudia, ID: 171.3.0025 (Box 55, Folder 17, Media ID: 171.3.0025)
    Wave Transformations, Documentation of Installations Rosalind Schneider
  - Smithson, Robert, 2005; ID: 171.3.0026 (Box 55, Folder 18, Media ID: 171.3.0026)
    Robt. Smithson, Floating Island, Sept. 2005
  - Smithson, Robert, 2005; ID: 171.3.0027 (Box 55, Folder 18, Media ID: 171.3.0027)
    Robt. Smithson, Floating Island, Sept. 2005, New York, NY
  - Smithson, Robert, 2005; ID: 171.3.0028 (Box 55, Folder 18, Media ID: 171.3.0028)
  - Sonnier, Keith, ID: 171.3.0029 (Box 55, Folder 19, Media ID: 171.3.0029)
    Keith Sonnier, 212-732-1481, ksstudio@mindspring.com, MTA FULTON STREET
  - Sonnier, Keith, ID: 171.3.0030 (Box 55, Folder 19, Media ID: 171.3.0030)
    Kulturforum Berlin Booklet, Keith Sonnier, ksstudio@mindspring.com
  - Tegeder, Dannielle, 2006; ID: 171.3.0031 (Box 55, Folder 20, Media ID: 171.3.0031)
    Dannielle Tegeder, Images of Work 2006, Priska C. Juschka Fine Art, New York
  - TOMI - Proposal, 2004; ID: 171.3.0032 (Box 55, Folder 21, Media ID: 171.3.0032)
    Aycock, 2 Proposals, 12/16/04
  - Wolf, Silvio, 2005; ID: 171.3.0033 (Box 55, Folder 22, Media ID: 171.3.0033)
    front cover: Silvio Wolf, Photoworks inside cover: Biography, 01-Angels of Time, 02-Horizons, 03-Icons of Light, 04-John 14, 05-Scala Zero, 06-Scale Reali, 07-Skylights, 08-Thresholds compact disk: Silvio Wolf, Copyright Silvio Wolf 2005 All rights reserved, Photoworks back cover: Silvio Wolf - VIA COMPAGNONI 3 - 20129 MILANO - ITALY, Tel/fax: +39.02713079, email: info@silviowolf.com
  - Wolf, Silvio, 2005; ID: 171.3.0034 (Box 55, Folder 22, Media ID: 171.3.0034)
    front cover: Silvio Wolf, Selected Works inside cover: 1-Public Art Works: Biography, 1987-Grande Muro Occidentale, 1990-Scala Reale, 199-Ikonenwerk, 1996-L'Osservanza, 1997-Stazione di Berlino, 1998-Luogo Parola, 1999-Grida dal Tempio, 1999-The Elsewhere, 2000-Annunciation, 2001-Angeli del Tempo, 2003-Loggia delle Parole, 2004-Pietra d'Aqua. 2-Site-Specific Installations: Biography, 1991-Stelle Braille, 1992-Baden-Baden, 1993-Laboratorio, 1995-Luci Bianche, 1996-Iconostasi, 1997-Ricreazione, 1999-Chantier-Marche', 1999-LaZone d'Ombre, 2001-Fondazione del Tempo, 2002-Oggi. 3-Photo Works: Biography, 01-Icons of Light, 02-Angels of Time, 03-Scala Zero, 04-Skylights, 05-Thresholds, 06-Horizons, 07-John 14. back cover: Silvio Wolf - VIA COMPAGNONI 3 - 20129 MILANO - ITALY, Tel/fax: +39.02713079, email: info@silviowolf.com
  - Yankowitz, Nina, 2001; ID: 171.3.0035 (Box 55, Folder 23, Media ID: 171.3.0035)
    Yankowitz and Holden, Projects 2001 NYAnkowitz@aol.com, 106 Spring Street, New York, NY, 10012, USA, 212/226-4375 Yankowitz and Holden copyright 8/20/01
  - Zhang, Jian-Jun and Edelstein, Barbara, ID: 171.3.0036 (Box 55, Folder 24, Media ID: 171.3.0036)
    Same compact disk and cover as found in Folder 7.
- Series IV: Media
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. For more information, please contact fales.library@nyu.edu. or call 212 998 2596.
  This series consists mainly of video material, with a minimal amount of audio and includes footage of conferences and artist installations.
  Scope and Contents notes at the item level include notations on videocassettes, and additional information found on sleeves.
  - Art Market Report, November 7, 1988; ID: 171.0001 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0001)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Original format: VHS
    Duration: 28 minutes
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - ART Today: A Publication of Arts Video News Service, undated; ID: 171.0002 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0002)
    Duration: unknown
  - ART Today: A Publication of Arts Video News Service, undated; ID: 171.0003 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0003)
  - Atwell Fine Art, Santa Fe, New Mexico, undated; ID: 171.0004 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0004)
    Duration: 12 minutes
    Subscription postcard included in case.
  - Cast in Bronze, undated; ID: 171.0005 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0005)
  - CHIHULY Video Set, undated; ID: 171.0006 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0006)
    Duration: 66 minutes
    KCTS 9 Chihuly Special CBS Sunday A.M. Team Chihuly at S.A.M. KCTS 9 Special - Pelleas & Melisande
  - Alessandro Diaz de Santillana: Machina Animae (Soul Tools), May 5, 1995 - May 28, 1995; ID: 171.0007 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0007)
    Duration: 10 minutes
  - OLYMPOS: 1996 Olympics Illumination, ID: 171.0008 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0008)
    Duration: 5 minutes
  - "Sculpture in Two Locations," Artist: Michel Gerard, undated; ID: 171.0009 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0009)
    A documentary by Neculai Burghelea
  - El Banquete Landing on Mars, undated; ID: 171.0010 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0010)
  - Interactive Architecture: Harmonic Runway, undated; ID: 171.0011 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0011)
    Duration: 8 minutes
  - Chris Janney, Studio 7, undated; ID: 171.0012 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0012)
  - Mystic, Scenic Studio, Inc., undated; ID: 171.0013 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0013)
  - Eric Orr: Prime Matter Works, undated; ID: 171.0014 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0014)
  - Liz Phillips: 2 Wind-Sound Pieces, undated; ID: 171.0015 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0015)
    Big Apple Minute S. Bronx Opening Windspun for Minneapolis
  - Gio' Pomodoro, Sculture A Firenze, undated; ID: 171.0016 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0016)
    Directed by Marco Agostinelli
  - Tim Prentice 3, undated; ID: 171.0017 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0017)
  - The Public Art Fund, undated; ID: 171.0018 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0018)
  - George Rickey Sculpture, undated; ID: 171.0019 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0019)
    Oblique Column of Twelve Open Squares I GYR. Two Conical Segments, Gyratory Gyratory II Two Lines Horizontal Gyratory Two Lines Oblique Down II Five Open Squares Gyratory Gyratory II Two Lines Up Oblique
  - Tony Robbin, undated; ID: 171.0020 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0020)
  - 60 Minutes Art, October 1997; ID: 171.0021 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0021)
  - "Metamorphosis" 1992 / "Magic Garden" 1990, Eric and Deborah Staller, 1992;1990; ID: 171.0022 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0022)
  - Space Time: Storm King, July 23, 1987; ID: 171.0023 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0023)
    Duration: 21 minutes
    Currently unavailable.
  - Images of Miyazaki, George Sugarman Japan Art Project, 1995; ID: 171.0024 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0024)
  - The Art of James Surls and Rom Ryan: "Parallel Directions", undated; ID: 171.0025 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0025)
    Producer: Herb Hochman
  - "Trans Potomac Canal Center", undated; ID: 171.0026 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0026)
    Duration: 11 minutes
  - "Transpotomac Canal Center," Savage/Fogarty Companies Inc., October 1986; ID: 171.0027 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0027)
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs..
    Produced by: The Blackwell Corporation, Washington DC
  - Fountains: Howard and Gay Ben Tre, undated; ID: 171.0028 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0028)
    Color
    Duration: 9 minutes
    Immanent Circumstance: Post Office Square Park, Boston, Massachusetts Playscape Fountain: Hasbro Children's Hospital, Providence, Rhode Island
  - Todd Warner Orlando Project, undated; ID: 171.0029 (Box 56, Media ID: 171.0029)
- OVERSIZE Series I: Artist Files
  - Acconci, Vito - "So the Plot Can Be Thickened..." (Photocopies), undated (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Acconci, Vito - Town Square Sculpture Proposals, 1987 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Albert and Vera List Visual Arts Center - Poster, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Allen, Terry - Proposals, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Baas, Maarten - Where There's Smoke Poster, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Batcheller, Ed - Proposals, undated (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Buchanan, Beverly - Poster, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Buren, Daniel - Poster, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Cooper, Ruffin Jr. - Poster, undated (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Ewing, Lauren - Proposals, 1995 (Folder 2 Left)
  - Fernendez, Terasita - Poster, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Fine, Judd & Barbara McCarren - Reviews, undated (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Fischer, Joel - Correspondence, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Gerard, Michael - Catalogue, 2003 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Graham, Dan - Proposal, undated (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Highstein, Jene - Posters, Proposals, Photos, 1988 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Hollis, Douglas - Proposals, 1996 (Folder 12)
  - Kotobuki - Kaufman: Proposals, undated (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - LeWitt, Sol - Catalogue, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Lin, Maya - Monroe Mall Proposal, undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Lipski, Donald - Proposals, undated (Folder 1 Left)
  - Louden, Sharon - Catalogue, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Lucier, Mary - Proposals, 1984 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Lucier, Mary - Reviews, 1982, 1987, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Messner, Ann - "Amniotic Sea", 1997 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Miyawaki, Aiko - Poster, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Mori, Mariko - Poster, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Morris, Robert - Blueprints, 1982 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Munoz, Celia Alvarez - Reviews, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Nahon, Brigitte - Poster, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Nash, David - Reviews, Posters, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Paik, Nam June - Photos, undated (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Pepper, Beverly - Reviews, 1989 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Pinto, Jody - Proposals, 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Poirier, Anne & Patrick - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Rist, Pippoloti - Poster, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Roesch, Robert - Gateway Plaza Proposals, undated (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Roesch, Robert - Proposals, 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Saret, Alan - Proposals, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Scanga, Italo - "A donkey-load of water buckets...", 1996 (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Serra, Richard - Poster, 2001 (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Shelton, Peter - Posters, 1986, 2006 (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Simpson, Buster - Reviews and Proposals, undated, 1996 (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Staller, Eric - Proposal, 1984 (Roll-storage 66)
  - Stuart, Michelle - Proposals, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Taho, Ritsuko - Catalogue, Posters, 1991, 1994 (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Varini, Felice - Reviews, undated (Box 53, Folder 34)
  - Venet, Bernard - Poster, undated (Box 53, Folder 35)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Poster, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 36)
  - Von Rydingsvard, Ursula - Proposals, 1983 (Box 53, Folder 37)
  - Webster, Meg - Catalogue, Proposals, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 38)
  - Weiner, Lawrence - Posters, 1999 (Box 53, Folder 39)
  - West, Franz - Poster, 2005 (Box 53, Folder 40)
  - Whitefort, Kate - Poster, 1992 (Box 53, Folder 41)
  - Whiteread, Rachel - Reviews, 1998 (Box 53, Folder 42)
  - Woodman, Betty - Posters, 1994, 1996, 2000 (Box 53, Folder 43)
- OVERSIZE Series II: Administrative Files
  - Art New England: A Resource for the Visual Arts, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Battery Park City, undated (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Battery Park City - Proposals, 1995 (Folder 9)
  - Battery Park City - Proposals, undated (Roll-storage 67)
  - City Art: Arvada, Dallas, Denver, New York, Philadelphia, Pittsburgh, Raleigh, undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - City Art: California, undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Arts Awards - Poster, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Greater Buffalo International Airport - Proposals, undated (Folder 8)
  - JPS Japan Trip, undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Kot: Niigata Hospital/Kaufmann Proposals, undated (Folder 7)
  - Kotsuda High School Project, undated (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Kotsuda High School Project - Proposals, undated (Folder 6)
  - The Livable City: Number 5/1 and Number 9/2, 1978-1982 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Penn Station: James A. Farley Building, undated (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Phoenix Arts - Vol. 1, no. 2, 1987-1988 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Phoenix Sky Harbor Center Public Art Master Plan, undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Public Art Review - Vol. 1, no. 2, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Roosevelt Island Waterfront Project - Proposals, undated (Roll-storage 68)
  - Terminal One: JFK International Airport Plans, undated (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - U.S. 1: Princeton's Business and Entertainment Journal, 1988 (Box 54, Folder 21)
- ACCRETION 2014 - Series I: Artists Files
  - Abakanowicz, Magdalena, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Acconci, Vito, undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Albers, Josef, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Allen, Terry, 1991 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Amoros, Grimanesa, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Antonakos, Stephen, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Appel, Karel, undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Arienti, Stefano, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Armajani, Siah, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - The Art Commission of the City of New York, undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Art for the City, 1967 January 26-March 11 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Art in General, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Artists Space, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - The Arts and Business Council, Inc., [1991] (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Aubi, Eileen, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - B.T.I., undated (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Barbeito, Pedro, 2000 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Barcelo, Miquel, 1985 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Barliant, Claire, 2006 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Batcheller, Ed, undated (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Battery Park City, undated (Box 58, Folder 21)